xtremez.com 2013-05-09

# Help Center About Us

## About Paintball-Online.com

We are one of the Internet's largest paintball stores with 1000's of products in stock and ready to ship. Started in 1995 by an avid paintball player and net-surfer, our goal is to utilize our low overhead and large buying power to bring you the best products at competitive prices with the convenience of secure online shopping. If you have questions feel free to contact us at (360) 567-2520. We love what we do and it shows in our service everyday! 

## Affiliate Program

Paintball-Online.com Affiliate Program provides paintball or extreme sports websites with the opportunity to earn money by turning their site visitors into Paintball-Online.com customers. 

When a visitor to your site clicks on a link that points to Paintball-Online.com a cookie with your unique tracking information is placed on their computer. Commission Junction is a respected industry leader that has a state of the art tracking system. 100% of your results are monitored. This information is accessible to you 24 hours a day through this trusted third party's web-site. 

There is no fee to join our program or Commission Junction. Affiliate commission starts at 5% and you can earn up to 10% depending on your monthly sales. 

## 30 Day Guarantee

We offer a 30-Day Money Back Guarantee on all new and unused merchandise, excluding paintballs and apparel, in its original packaging. We offer 120% Price Protection for 30 Days from your order Most manufactures provide a 1-Year full parts and labor warranty on merchandise. (Call for details) All Paintball sales are final. Breakage is insured in shipment. 

## 120% Price Protection

Paintball-Online.com is never beat on price. If you find a lower price within 30 days of your order, we will gladly refund you 120% of the difference in price. For example, if you purchased an item for $149.99, then found it for $119.99 (a $30 difference), we would refund you $36.00.

Price Protection does not apply to reseller's liquidations, where the other retailer is backordered or out-of-stock, closeouts, local paintball stores (we can't verify) or below cost loss leaders. Paintball Online will not match it's own price. This policy does not apply to purchases at Paintball-Online.com retail locations. Not valid with any other offer. 

## Contact Information

**Email:** sales@paintball-online.com  
**Order Hotline:** (800) 875-4547  
**Order Status:** +1 (360) 567-2520  
(Monday - Saturday: 9am - 6pm Pacific Time)  
**Fax:** (360) 567-1766  
**Mailing Address:** 1212 W. Fourth Plain Blvd, Vancouver, WA 98660 USA 

## Directions to an Xtremez near you

Visit one of our retail locations: Vancouver, WA Tualatin, OR 

## Jobs

Love paintball? Live in the Northwest? [Join the Paintball Online team.](http://www.paintball-online.com/pages/viewpage.aspx?page=20)

## Lowest Price Guarantee

Low price guarantee does not apply to resellers' liquidations, backorders/out-of-stocks, closeouts, local paintball stores or below cost loss leaders. Only one price match per item will be processed. Paintball Online will not match it's own price. This policy does not apply to purchases at PaintballOnline.com retail locations. Not valid with any other offers. 

## Wholesale Inquiries

Field and store owners [apply](http://wholesale.paintball-online.com/) for a wholesale account today! 

## Information Collection and Use

Paintball-online.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. paintball-online.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

## Order

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user may not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, (paintball-online.com) are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

## Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site or a product, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. paintball-online.com will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to visit the site. paintball-online.com stores this information for sending this email and to notify them of future promotions. The friend may contact paintball-online.com at http://www.paintball-online.com/store/contact.asp to request the removal of this information from their database.

## Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to security@paintball-online.com

## Special Offers

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

## Site and Service Updates

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

## Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support

## Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an opt-out mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at sales@paintball-online.com. Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

## PowerReviews Program

Paintball-Online has arranged with PowerReviews, Inc. (d/b/a Buzzillions) ("PowerReviews") to facilitate the collection of customer product reviews on products sold by paintball-online.com. When you submit a product review to paintball-online.com, you are also subject to PowerReviews' terms of use and privacy policies (see [Buzzillions Privacy Policy](http://www.buzzillions.com/public/legal/privacy_policy_en_US.html)). Accordingly, you should review those policies prior to submitting a review. Also, reviews you submit may be posted on both [Buzzillions.com](http://www.buzzillions.com/) and our site.
